RG 062:161, Town of Wilton
Connecticut State Library
Town of Wilton records
1942-1972
Connecticut State Library
Wilton (Conn.)
.5 cubic feet
Military and election records for the town of Wilton.
RG062_161
2013-001
Historical Note
The town of Wilton was incorporated in May 1802 and was taken from Norwalk. The town is located in Fairfield County.
Scope and Content
Military discharge papers, 1942, 1944-1947, 1949, 1952-1956, 1958-1961, 1966; Voter registration applications, 1944-1946, 1948, 1950, 1952, 1954, 1957-1960, 1963-1970, 1972. These application forms are called "Application by Member of the Armed Forces of the United States for Absentee Admission as an Elector" through January 1966. After that the forms are called "Application for Absentee Admission as an Elector".
Arrangement
The militrary discharge papers are arranged alphabetically by last name. The voter registration applications are arranged chronologically by approval/denial date.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Military discharge -- Connecticut; Voter registration -- Connecticut -- Wilton
Places:
Wilton (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Application forms; Military records
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
Series 1, Military Records. Connecticut General Statutes §1-219 restricts veteran’s military records including but not limited to a DD 214 form for 75 years. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Military Records, 1942-1966
  - Military discharge papers, 1942-1966
    RESTRICTED
    Connecticut General Statutes §1-219 restricts veteran’s military records including but not limited to a DD 214 form for 75 years. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Military discharge papers: A-D (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Military discharge papers: F-L (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Military discharge papers: M-R (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Military discharge papers: S (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Military discharge papers: T-Y (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series 2. Election Records, 1944-1972
  - Voter registration applications, 1944-1972
    - Voter registration applications, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Voter registration applications, 1945-1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Voter registration applications, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Voter registration applications, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Voter registration applications, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)